

Do Tuan Vuong

Date of Birth: 12th October 1992

Mobile: 01687 482 737 Email: vuongdt92@gmail.com 58/2/19st Le Hong Phong

Ward 2 District 5

Profile

I graduated IT in University of Science HCM city

I'm developer java

I am a hardworking, proficient IT with 1 years' experience and a real passion for Java development.

Readily embracing cutting-edge technology. Having helped develop a few successful apps java web and java android. I am seeking a new opportunity that will allow me to further expand on these skills.

Experiences Summary

Employee Maper JSC

System Engineer

August 4, 2015 - now

- Java android
- Java Spring framework

I developed app Collector, you see on the address https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.maper.datacollection

I joined develop system back-end for android app.

Employee of WeebPal .Co http://www.weebpal.com/

Java android Developer

April 6, 2015 - June 26, 2015

• Fresher Engineer

Internship of Global CyberSoft .Co

Java Web Developer

April 2014 – July 2014

Internship

Mobile Developer

Mobile Developer March 2014 – Present

- Develop App Appointment Management.
- Develop App Outdoor Management.
- Develop App Capture, Management Photo.

Java Web Developer

Java Web Developer

September 2014 – Present

- Develop Web Sales.
- Develop Web Management Employees

Skills Summary

Program languages

- Javascript
- CSS
- Java Spring Framework, Hibernate, Java servlet, JSP.
- Android platform
- Android SDK
- Java android
- C, C++, C#
- SQL Server, My SQL, SQLite, MongoDB

Technical Skill

- Object-oriented Programming
- Requirement Analysis
- Software Analysis and Design
- Software Project Management
- MVP, MVC pattern

Software Skill

- Platform: Windows
- Developing tool: Eclipse, Visual Studio, Rational Rose, NetBeans,

Language Skill

- Listening: IntermediateSpeaking: Intermediate
- Reading: Good
- Writing: Intermediate

Qualifications

- Developer Java Web Applications
- Developer Android Applications

Education

• 2011 – 2015 University of Science HCM.

Degree: Information Technology – Software Technical.

• 02/2013 – 03/2013 Scrum course of Axon Active VN.

Degree: Scrum development model